addataexpress.com 2018-10-28

# Privacy Policy - Winmo

### Introduction

  1. This Privacy and Cookies Policy sets out the privacy and cookies policy of List Partners, LLC, whose  
registered address is 3098 Piedmont Rd, Suite 200 Atlanta, GA, USA 30305 and its product Winmo,  
who controls this website. For the purpose of the Data Protection Act, the data controller is List  
Partners LLC.
  2. List Partners is committed to protecting the privacy of its users and the purpose of this Privacy  
Policy is to describe to you how List Partners will use personal information about you that is  
submitted to List Partners.
  3. By providing your personal information to List Partners, you consent to the collection and use of it  
and any other information provided to List Partners in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If at any  
time you wish to change the uses of your personal information to which you have consented, please  
contact us at [support@thelistinc.com](mailto:support@thelistinc.com).
  4. List Partners may revise this Privacy Policy at any time by posting an update on its website(s).  
Please ensure that you check this website and any other List Partners website(s) you use from time  
to time to review the then current Privacy Policy and to update your preferences. This Privacy and  
Cookies Policy was last updated in May, 2018.

### Collection of Personal Information

  1. List Partners collects information provided by you when you register to use our site or subscribe to  
our services. The types of personal information collected and stored by List Partners might include  
your name, business title, business e-mail address, business postal address, business telephone  
number, business fax number and business credit/debit card details (to the extent permitted by the  
Data Protection Act 1998 and related legislation (“the DPA”).
  2. List Partners (or any of its sub-contractors) may collect personal information about you in the  
following ways: 
    1. any data which you provide when you complete and submit an application to List  
Partners to register on its website(s) or receive email alerts, publications or other  
communications from List Partners or register to attend one of its events;
    2. any data that you provide via postings to forums and blogs and any other posting that  
you make to a List Partners websites (in such circumstances the information posted by  
you will, of course, also be available to users of the website throughout the world);  
during any transaction with us; and
    3. any other data which you provide to List Partners when you enquire about our  
activities, email, telephone or write to us or otherwise provide us with personal  
information.
  3. List Partners (or any of its sub-contractors) may also receive information about you from third  
parties, for example a colleague who wants to tell you about one of our websites. 

### Storage and retention of your information

  1. List Partners will keep your information on a secure server. The technology that List Partners uses  
and the security policies which List Partners has implemented are intended to safeguard your  
information from unauthorized access and improper use.
  2. List Partners will keep your information (to the extent permitted by the DPA) to enable List  
Partners to use it for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.

### Use of Your Information

  1. List Partners may use your personal information (subject in each case to the requirements of the  
DPA) for the following purposes: 
    1. administering your website account(s) and otherwise in connection with any service for which  
you have provided your information, including any email alerts, subscriptions ii) to publications,  
attendance at events, transactions with us and competitions and promotions that you take part  
in; responding to any enquiry you make;
    2. subject to your consent, sending you newsletters and/or alerts and information regarding List  
Partners or any third party’s future services (in all formats to which you have consented e.g.  
post, email, text); and
    3. for generating aggregated statistics about users, traffic patterns etc. of the List Partners  
website(s) and other services and developing List Partners marketing plans.
  2. List Partners may also disclose your information (subject in each case to the requirements of the  
DPA) as follows: 
    1. if you have given your consent for List Partners to do so, to other selected organizations to  
enable them to contact you or send you information by post, telephone and/or email;
    2. to any service providers, sub-contractors and agents appointed by List Partners to perform  
the above functions on its behalf and in accordance with its instructions;
    3. to third parties selected by List Partners as part of aggregated and anonymized statistics  
about users, traffic patterns etc. of the List Partners website(s);
    4. to such individuals and/or bodies as necessary to ensure List Partners compliance with any  
applicable law, regulation, legal proceeding or governmental request;
    5. (where you post material that does or may constitute a criminal offence, breach the rights of  
a third party, give rise to a civil action or breach the Terms & Conditions of the applicable  
website and as otherwise necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of List Partners and  
its customers), to any relevant authority or third party requiring List Partners to disclose the  
identity of or locate anyone posting such material on a List Partners website;
    6. To other members of List Partners group (which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding  
company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the Companies Act 2006); and to any  
individual making a subject information request to List Partners
  3. In the event that List Partners (or a relevant part of List Partners) is acquired by or merges with  
another company, your personal information may be passed to the purchasing/merging company  
amongst the transferred business assets. This will enable your relationship to continue with the  
relevant List Partners business despite the change of ownership. Your personal information may also  
be passed (on a confidential basis) to companies with whom List Partners is negotiating such a  
sale/merger as part of the verification exercise carried out on List Partners by the third party. 
  4. In processing your information in accordance with the above, List Partners may (to the extent  
permitted by the DPA) send it outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”) including the United  
States of America. List Partners will take all reasonable steps to ensure that in such circumstances  
your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy but your attention is drawn to  
the fact that the laws of countries outside the EEA may provide lesser protection to your information  
than the UK. When you submit your personal information to List Partners you consent to the transfer  
of your information outside the EEA unless you specifically indicate otherwise. 

### Cookies

When you visit a List Partners website(s), List Partners uses “cookie” technology try to make that  
experience simple, personalized and meaningful. Cookies are small pieces of information which are  
issued to your computer or any similar device you use to access the internet e.g. smart phone, tablet  
or other mobile device when you visit a website and which store and sometimes track information  
about you’re use of the website. A number of cookies List Partners use last only for the duration of  
your web session and expire when you close your browser. Other cookies are used to remember you  
when you return to the website and will last for longer.

List Partners uses cookies to:

  * create a specific log-in session for a visitor to a List Partners website in order that page requests by that visitor are delivered in an effective, secure and consistent manner;
  * recognize when a visitor to a List Partners website has visited before; this means we can identify  
the number of unique visitors we receive to the website and allows us to make sure we have  
enough capacity for the number of users that we get;
  * customize elements of the promotional layout and/or content of the pages of the website;
  * store your product selections to the shopping basket;
  * collect statistical information about how our visitors use the website(s) so that we can improve the  
website(s) and learn which parts are most popular to visitors; and
  * gather information through our advertising partners, about the pages on the List Partners  
website(s) that you visit, and also other information about other websites that you visit, so as to  
place you in an “interest segment”. This information is then used to serve interest-based  
advertisements which it is believed will be targeted to your interests. For more information about  
this type of interest based advertising, and about how to turn this feature off please visit  
www.youronlinechoices.co.uk or follow the link to the website of our advertising partners shown  
below. Without these cookies, advertisements you encounter will be less relevant to you and to  
your interests.

Some of the cookies used by List Partners websites are set by us, and some are set by third parties  
who are delivering services on our behalf. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies but, if  
you prefer, you can change your browser to prevent that or to notify you each time a cookie is set.  
You can also learn more about cookies by visiting www.allaboutcookies.org which includes additional  
useful information on cookies and how to block cookies using different types of browser. Please note  
however, that by blocking or deleting cookies used on a List Partners website(s) you may not be able  
to take full advantage of the website(s) if you do so.

### Third Party Websites

Please be aware that List Partners does not control and is not responsible for websites that are  
referred to or linked from its own websites and that use of your personal information on these  
websites is not subject to this Privacy and Cookies Policy.

### Registration

  1. To access certain parts of the List Partners websites, List Partners may require you to register and  
provide certain information about yourself.
  2. You are reminded that in addition to the provisions of this Privacy and Cookies Policy, where you  
register you also agree to: 
    1. provide true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself as prompted by the  
relevant registration form (such information being the “Registration Data”); and
    2. maintain and promptly update the Registration Data to keep it fully up to date.
